programadvisor.com 2007-08-21

# ProgramAdvisor

## Privacy Policy

### Our Commitment to Privacy

Our Privacy Policy was developed as an extension of our commitment to combine the highest-quality products and services with the highest level of integrity in dealing with our visitors, members, and partners. It is designed not only to assist you in understanding how we collect, use, and safeguard the personal information you provide to us, but also to help you in making informed decisions when using our Site and our products and services. This Privacy Policy will be continuously assessed against new technologies, business practices, and our customers' needs.

Access to and use of the ProgramAdvisor.com Web site is available only to United States residents who can form legally binding contracts under applicable law. If you do not qualify, you may not use our Web site. If you are a minor, you may use the ProgramAdvisor.com Web site only in conjunction with your parent, legal guardian, or other responsible adult supervision. We urge supervising adults to actively oversee minors' online use. We do not sell, rent, or share personal information about you with other companies except to provide products and services you've requested, when we have your permission, or when we have a trusted partner who works on behalf of or with ProgramAdvisor.com under confidentiality agreements to help ProgramAdvisor.com communicate with you about offers from us or our marketing partners. However, these partners operating under confidentiality agreements do not have any independent right to use or share this information.

You agree that by submitting communications through the ProgramAdvisor.com Web site, no confidential, fiduciary, contractually implied, or other relationship is created between you and ProgramAdvisor.com other than pursuant to this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to the terms and conditions of our User Agreement . Like most websites, communications to, from and through the ProgramAdvisor.com Web site are not confidential, and your communications may be read or intercepted by others.

### A Note About Minors

In compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998, no one under 13 years of age can use our Web site. If you are a minor between the ages of 13 and 18, you may use our Site only in conjunction with your parent, legal guardian, or other responsible adult.

### What Information Do We Collect?

The goal of the ProgramAdvisor.com Web site is to be your favorite law enforcement destination on the Internet by providing you with the information, services and product offerings that are most relevant to you. To achieve this goal, we collect two types of information from you when you visit our Site: personally identifiable information you voluntarily choose to disclose, and "aggregate information" about your use of our Site that is automatically collected when you visit the ProgramAdvisor.com Web site.

### 1\. Personal Information You Choose to Provide

Personally identifiable information refers to information that tells us specifically who you are. Personal information is collected when you voluntarily choose to become a member of the ProgramAdvisor.com Web site community. As a member, you are asked to provide certain basic information such as your name, current email address, and service affiliation. You may also provide additional personal information at your option. Further, if you choose to correspond with us through email, we may retain the content of your email messages together with your email address and our responses.

### How Do We Use The Personal Information That You Provide To Us?

Broadly speaking, your personal information is used to help us customize the content and layout of our Web site so that we may provide you with a smooth and efficient visit. We also use personal information for purposes of administering our business activities, providing customer service, and making available other products and services to our customers and prospective customers. Occasionally, we may also use the information we collect to notify you about important changes to our Web site, new services, and special offers we think you will find valuable.

### 2\. Aggregate Information

Aggregate information refers to information your computer automatically provides to us and that cannot be tied back to you as a specific individual. Examples include referral data (the web sites you visited just before and just after our Web site), the pages viewed, time spent at our Web site, browser and platform type (e.g., a Netscape browser on a Macintosh platform), and IP (Internet Protocol) addresses. An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you surf the Web. When you request a page from one of our Sites, our servers log your IP address to create aggregate reports on user demographics and traffic patterns for advertisers and partners, and for purposes of system administration. This allows these parties to advertise more effectively, and allows you to receive advertisements that are more relevant.

### 3\. "Cookies"

The ProgramAdvisor.com Web site, along with thousands of other web sites, uses standard technologies, such as "cookies" and web server logs, to enhance your web viewing experience. Cookies and web server logs automatically track certain information about you that is based upon your activity on our Site. A cookie is a small piece of data transferred from a web site to the hard drive of your computer so that the web site may track your activities on the site. Web server logs allow us to count how many people visit our Web site and also to evaluate our Site's visitor capacity.

Each time you access our Site, our server may deliver certain customized information to you based on the data stored in your cookies. Cookies allow us to determine which areas and features of our Site are most popular by measuring user activity. Cookies let sites and advertisers "remember" users across pages of a site and across multiple visits to a site. This allows e-commerce and Internet advertising to: personalize features such as targeted news stories, remember user names and passwords for future visits, control ad frequency or the number of times a user sees a given ad, and deliver advertisements targeted to a user's interests. Your computer may occasionally receive cookies from our advertisers. ProgramAdvisor.com does not control these cookies, and they are not subject to our Privacy Policy. You can disable cookies, but access to certain parts of our Web site may no longer be available to you. Cookies can be disabled. The Help portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether.

### Sharing Information With Co-Brand Service Providers

ProgramAdvisor.com offers a number of third party services from our Site, such as ecommerce stores for law enforcement gear and the job board. If you choose to use these optional services, we may provide some of your personally identifiable information to the Co-Brand Service Provider offering such services in order for them to provide the service. Conversely, the Co-Brand Service Provider may provide ProgramAdvisor.com with personal information about you.

### Sharing Information With Affiliated Businesses, Strategic Partners, Subsidiaries, Advertisers, And Other Third Parties

We may enter into strategic marketing alliances with third parties, such as strategic partners and subsidiaries, who may be given access to personal information, including your name, address, and email, for the purpose of providing you with information about products and services that may be of interest to you. We evaluate such partners to identify products and services that serve the needs of our members well. We cannot and do not, however, make any representations about the practices and policies of these companies.

### Information Collected In Ad Delivery

We use a third-party advertising company to serve ads when you visit our Web site. This company may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visit to this Web site in order to provide advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you. In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by this company, please click here.

### Notice Of New Services And Changes

Occasionally, we may also use the information we collect to notify you about important changes to our Web site, new services, and special offers we think you will find valuable. If you would not like to receive these notifications, you can remove yourself from these lists at any time at your member management page.

### How Do We Protect Your Information?

We utilize encryption/security software to safeguard the confidentiality of personal information we collect. This software provides a limited degree of protection against unauthorized access or disclosure, as well as accidental loss, alteration, or destruction.

### Do We Comply With Legally Compelled Disclosure Of Information?

We may release any private information about you that we possess when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, to enforce or apply the terms and conditions of our User Agreement, Privacy Policy and/or other agreements, or to protect the rights, property or safety of ProgramAdvisor.com, our Site users, or others.

### What About Other Web Sites Linked to or from Our Web Site?

The links in the ProgramAdvisor.com Web site allow you to leave our Site. Please be aware that once you leave our Site and enter another web site, our Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. Your browsing and interaction on web sites that have a link to our Web site, or any links contained in a linked site, is subject to that web site's own rules and policies. ProgramAdvisor.com is not responsible for the privacy practices employed by these sites, nor the information or content contained therein. We provide these links to you only as a convenience, and the inclusion of any link does not imply endorsement by ProgramAdvisor.com of the site. Please read over the rules and policies of these sites before proceeding. If you have concerns about any site that is linked on ProgramAdvisor.com, please contact us

### Changes to Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes here so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information, and to whom we will disclose it. If at any time, you have questions or concerns about our Privacy Policy, please feel free to email us at info@ProgramAdvisor.com.

You acknowledge that upon entering your email address and thus becoming a member of ProgramAdvisor.com, you are automatically subscribed to receive newsletters and notifications including but not limited to updates on your membership, community news, or benefits information. If you would not like to receive these communications, you can remove yourself from these lists at any time at your Member Management page.
